# **Andrew Nowak**

### **Self-led aspiring IT Professional**

Las Vegas, NV 89130 andrewnowak@live.com 702-292-0875

Self-led aspiring IT Professional with 3+ years of experience within an end-user technical support role, with a deep knowledge base of internal computer hardware along with operating systems and how they interact with the hardware. My daily drive is to continue learning and developing to become an IT Professional.

I am currently finishing my CompTIA A+ and Networking+ Certifications along with Google's IT Support Professional Certificate.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

# **Premier Support Solutions Technician**

Asurion - Las Vegas, NV March 2018 to Present

- o Provided end-user support for a variety of mobile device(s), computers and their reported issues.
- o Documented customer interactions with effective documentation
- o Diagnose Networking Interaction within Verizons internal platform and user accounts
- o Kept a positive manner and friendly tone throughout interactions with end-user
- o Led and provided internal support for new hire(s) within a training environment
- o Always kept up with the newest technology with self-led trainings to be able to provide answers for one off questions from end-users
- o Supported and Troubleshot Windows, Android, iOS, macOS, ChromeOS systems.

# LOCAL MARKET DRIVER/FIELD RESEARCH ANALYST

Xceligent, Inc - Las Vegas, NV April 2017 to December 2017

103 SE Magellan Dr, Blue Springs, MO 64014

- o Researching local commercial real estate
- o Working with top local brokers in the area to gather information, while driving around town and researching sales
- o Updated photographs of buildings by taking new pictures of each building I visited
- o Weekly office calls with sales department and analytics team
- o Company filed for Chapter 7 Bankruptcy as of 12/14/2017

#### **CASHIER/SHIFT LEADER**

Dunkin Donuts - Las Vegas, NV July 2014 to March 2017 5485 Simmons St, Las Vegas, NV 89031

- o Money handling when deposits needed to be made
- o Entire store inventory when needed
- o Training new hires as needed
- o Cashing out drawers at end of day
- o Managed crew members daily

#### **CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE**

Kickback, Co - Las Vegas, NV April 2016 to September 2016

2950 South Rancho, Las Vegas, NV 89102

- o Assisted in setting up office, with computer stations, TV's, telephones, as well as security for the building
- o Customer Service Representative
- o Handled inbound and outbound emails and full service ticket system
- o Laid off due to company closing Las Vegas office

# Education

#### **HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA**

Shadow Ridge High School - Las Vegas, NV  $2010\ \text{to}\ 2014$ 

### Skills

- TRAINING (2 years)
- 70 WPM (Less than 1 year)
- Microsoft Office (5 years)
- TEACHING (Less than 1 year)
- Detailing
- Analytics
- Help Desk
- Computer Networking
- Mobile Devices
- Technical Support
- IT Support
- Android
- Operating Systems
- Network Support
- Desktop Support
- Microsoft Windows

# Additional Information

#### Skills & Abilities

#### **MANAGEMENT**

• Experience as a Shift Leader at Dunkin Donuts, managing all crew members in their work, helping direct crew members where they are needed, and training them as they progress at the store.

### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

• Proficient at Microsoft Office (and/or Keynote), Helping with Web Building, along with 70 WPM (Average)

### COMMUNICATION

 $\bullet$  Has exceptional communication skills in the workplace, and able to adapt to change along with teaching

others about the change